本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 粟  小笼包  小妖怪  小飞鱼  倾城小腊肉
校对|后期： 莫若谦
以下是上星期的《无耻之徒》
For all of you who were too fucking busy,
送给你们这些太他妈忙的人
this is what happened last week on Shameless.
为什么那人开走你的车
Why is that man driving your car?
你就这么让他偷走了
You let him steal it?
不 贝托 是我偷的
No, Beto, I stole it,
那时我的生活还是多姿多彩的
back when life was fun and the world had meaning.
我的伴侣为这城市工作
My partner works for this city.
但只是因为我们没有结婚
Because we're not married,
便不能共享他的保险福利
I'm not allowed to share in his insurance benefits.
你告诉全世界我们是同性恋
You told the world we're gay.
你 我的朋友 迈出了
You, my friend, have stumbled into
同性恋权利运动中
the most significant moment
最重要的历史性的一步
in the history of the gay rights movement.
你现在是一脸狗屎
You also have dog shit on your face
无家可归
and no place to live,
如果你愿意帮助我们 我们也愿意帮助你
but we can fix that, if you agree to work with us.
看看米奇 搞大一个妓女的肚子 要和对方结婚
And look at Mickey, marrying some whore he knocked up.
是真的吗 你要结婚
So is it true? You're getting married?
你爱我
You love me.
而且你是同性恋 你就承认吧
And you're gay. Just admit it.
就这一次 你承认吧
Just this once, admit it. Ugh!
- 你是临时工 - 是啊 你好
- You're the temp? - Yeah, hi.
我是菲奥娜 盖拉格
Yes. Fiona Gallagher.
办公室里有些贱人要打你的小报告
Some of the office bitches may have narced on you
是关于你电脑上那些成人照片和你的私人电话
about the porn at your desk and the personal phone calls.
普拉特先生要找你谈话
Well, Mr. Pratt is asking for a word with you.
- 我被炒鱿鱼了吗 - 不 你...你是...
- Am I fired? - No, you're... you're...
不管任何理由 你的桌子上不能再出现
No more naked body parts at your desk
裸露的人体部位
for any reason.
- 好的 -还有
- Got it. - And also,
你做得很棒
you're doing a great job.
刚想着要见你
Just the man I was hoping to run into.
我不能再见你了 我现在是和曼迪一起
I can't see you anymore. I'm with Mandy now.
- 是谁 - 我是凯伦杰克逊
- Who's this? - It's Karen Jackson.
- 操 - 你是说
- Fuck you. - Oh, you mean, like,
我们三个一起
all three of us?
下一次我问问利普的意见吧
Do you want me to ask Lip next time we do it?
好了 不好意思 妈妈
Okay, I'm sorry, mom.
是利普 他约在公园见面
It's... it's Lip. He wants to meet at the park.
你撞了谁
What'd you hit?
学校的一个女生
Girl at school.
无耻之徒 第三季第10集
# 回想你所得到的运气 #
think of all the luck you got
# 你并不是命途多舛 #
know that it's not for naught
# 你曾笑容满面 #
you were beaming once before
# 但已不曾再现 #
but it's not like that anymore
# 曾经的落魄 #
what is this downside
# 何以形容 #
that you speak of?
# 你如此肯定的 #
what is this feeling
# 是什么样的感受 #
you're so sure of?
# 召集你所有的朋友 #
round up the friends you got
# 你并不是孤身一人 #
know that they're not for naught
# 你曾心甘付出 #
you were willing once before
# 但已不曾再现 #
but it's not like that anymore
# 曾经的落魄 #
what is this downside
# 何以形容 #
that you speak of?
# 你如此肯定的 #
what is this feeling
# 是什么样的感受 #
you're so sure of?
你觉得乔治华盛顿和多少仆人发生过性关系
How many slaves you think George Washington had sex with?
卡尔 吃饭 现在
Carl, eat. Now.
比林肯多 比杰斐逊少
More than Lincoln, less than Jefferson.
伊恩 那淤青看起来好多了
Ian, that bruise is looking better.
- 你又被谁打了 - 没人
- Who beat you up again? - No one.
是在训练营 训练肉搏战
It's ROTC, practicing hand-to-hand.
水军还用拳头打架吗
Marines still fight with their fists?
特殊情况下 是的
In certain situations, yes.
如果我们不用核武器打架
What's the point of building nukes
- 那为什么要造核武器 - 国民生产总值
- if we ain't nuking anybody? - Gross National Product.
我能用昨晚吃剩的鸡骨头做汤吗
Can I use last night's chicken bones to make soup?
不是垃圾桶里的就行
As long as they're not in the trash.
利普有凯伦的新消息吗
Lip hear anything new about Karen?
还在睡
Still asleep.
凯伦还是利普
Karen or Lip?
俩
Both.
又早起 还吃早餐了 真不错
Up and at 'em, yet again. Impressive.
有工作就是这样
Having a job does that to me.
你重新照顾利亚姆可以吗
You good with Liam duty again today?
我和利亚姆骨子里就是好兄弟
Me and Liam are deeply bonded bros.
我能和你说几句话吗
Hey, can I talk to you for a sec?
当然 你可以和我一起走吗
Uh, yeah, cool. Can you walk with me?
可以啊
Yeah.
- 晚点见 - 再见
- Mwa. Bye, see you later. - Bye.
- 再见 - 乖乖地和吉米一起
- Bye! - Be good for Jimmy.
嘿 这儿 谢谢
Hey, here. Thanks.
我就告诉你标题行吗
How 'bout I just give you the headline?
可以啊 报童 给我标题
Sure, newsboy. Headline away.
好的
Okay.
"建立更好的世界"
"Helping the world be a better place."
怎么说
Yeah, how's that?
我在考虑重回医学院
I'm thinking about going back to medical school.
什么
What?
我已经完成了两年 只剩下一年了
I already finished two years, only have one to go.
感觉这对我们都好
I'm just thinking it might be the right thing to do for us.
未来之类的 稳定的工作
Future and all. Stability.
医学院不是很难吗 而且很贵
Isn't med school really hard? And expensive?
但回报高
Yes, but the payoff's great.
六位数 我可以贷款
Six figures, and I'll take out loans.
如果不行 我就拖欠着
Doesn't work out, I'll just default.
"吉米医生" 是吗
"Doctor Jimmy," huh?
是啊 听起来比较蠢
Yeah, spit-balling.
好吧 我要去给有需要的人
Okay. Well, I'm off to sell cups
卖杯子了
to people that use them.
可没有去医学院那么有趣
Not as exciting as medical school,
但还是挺好玩的
but exciting nonetheless.
嘿
Hey.
好了 开始吧
Okay, let's get started.
你们知道此行的目的
You all know why you're here.
你们在新闻上在推特上脸书上
You've seen his story on the news,
看到了他的故事
on Twitter feeds, on your Facebook walls.
他的一生都未曾出柜
His is a tale of a lifetime in the closet,
可他做出了勇敢的决定 接受了他的本性
of a brave midlife embrace of his true nature,
在至关重要的公民权利的问题上
and an acknowledgment that he is a lightning rod
他成为了避雷针
for a vital civil rights issue.
女士们先生们 有请弗兰克盖拉格
Ladies and gentlemen, Frank Gallagher.
弗兰克
Frank?
我们正... 我们正处于我们国家历史中的
We're at a... we are at a crucial time
关键时刻
in our nation's history.
此时 我们只能把国家往正确的方向推动
Where, as a nation, we'll either pivot toward what's right...
否则... 即被困在这错误的境地
or, um... stay stuck in what's wrong,
并且不允许犯错 现在 成为同性恋是一件可怕的事
and make no mistake, right now, it's a horrible time to be gay.
而我 就像你们一样 直接地感受到这种可怕
And I, like all of you, have experienced it firsthand.
显然 我引起了一场骚动
Apparently, I've caused a ruckus
因为我说同性恋们应该拥有公民权利
because I said that gay folks deserve certain civil rights...
拥有那些饲养员不希望给予我的权利
rights that the breeders don't want to bestow upon me.
哈哈哈 给予我们
Ha, ha, ha. Upon we.
那些饲养员 只是想阻止我们发生性关系
Those breeders, all they wanna do is stop us
因为他们得不到
from having the sex that they wish they were having.
如果...
If... if...
如果我们所发生的性关系惹到他们生气了
if the kind of sex we're having is what offends them most,
那他们就应该允许我们结婚
they should let us get married,
因为结了婚的人都知道
'cause anybody who's been married
婚姻是性的下坡
knows that the sex is downhill from there.
现在 这么久以来... 谢谢 这么久以来 我们都被误解了
Now, we have long... thank you. We have long been wronged,
现在是时候立法
and it's time for legislation
允许我们的私处为挑逗我们的人
that allows our private parts to be aroused
而雄起
by the people God intended to arouse them.
并且...
And...
并且是时候让它们在婚姻的束缚下雄起
and it's time for that arousal to happen within marriage!
请拿出你们男人的钱包
So get out your wallets, or your... your man purses,
来捐款吧
or whatever, and give now,
因为我不想再在早上雄起
'cause I hope never to be up again this early,
却没有你们在身旁
unless it's rolling over with a couple of you in bed.
谢谢 我爱你们
Thank you. I love you.
我勒个去 你真厉害 你是怎么变这么厉害的
Shit, you're good! How did you get so good?
我这一辈子 都在努力地说服人们
My whole life, I've been trying to convince people
去做他们不想做的事
to do what they really don't want to do.
那封... 大方的先生
The... the envelope, kind sir?
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
现在我们来谈一下为我的房间升级
Now, we gotta talk about upgrading my room.
你可以用我最近努力赚回来的钱
Uh, you can tip the front desk
给前台一些小费
with some of my recently departed hard-earned cash.
便捷商务旅馆的前台
The front desk at the Merchant Motor Inn
在防子弹的玻璃后面
is behind bulletproof glass.
那是树脂玻璃
It's plexiglass.
你有一张大床和许多付费频道
You have a queen bed and premium channels.
你刚见证了我的能力 我是你新的游说者了
You saw what I did here. I'm your new rainmaker.
我能让这些用屁股交易的人每天每夜都给你递现金
I can get these rump-swappers to cough up cash night and day.
"用屁股交易的人"
"Rump-swappers"?
这诋毁我还从来没听过
There's a slur I've never heard before.
好吧 先看看高中的演讲怎么样
Okay, we'll see how the high school speech goes,
在那儿之前 你还需要工作
but until then, you're still on the clock,
现在去和大家握手 你这个用屁股交易的小伙
so go shake some hands, ya little rump-swapper.
你这个小调皮
You saucy tart, you.
不好意思
Sorry about that.
很正常
It happens.
如果不是你 我可以...
Look, it's not you. I just, I...
我没办法不去想凯伦撞车
I can't get Karen getting hit by that car out of my mind.
嘿
Hey.
等等 我可以专心的
Hey, wait a minute. I can focus.
我上学要迟到了 午饭时间我们可以到
I'm late for school. We can give each other head
足球场的罩棚下再来一次
in the shed behind the football field at lunch.
罩棚那儿连低头都很难
It is hard to turn down head in the shed,
但我午饭的时候可能去不了
but I might not make it there by lunch.
要去一下医院 看看凯伦怎么样
Gotta stop by the hospital, see if Karen's okay.
她还没醒
She's in a coma.
我知道 我只是... 去给点支持
No, I know, I just... wanna show some support.
她都不知道你去了
She won't even know that you're there.
但还是去一下吧
Still, it's the right thing to do.
你想我和你一起去吗
Well, you want me to come with?
不用
No, I'm cool.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
你的额头起皱纹了
Your brow is furrowed.
哦 正常的时候就这样
Oh, that's its natural state.
其实是我男朋友
Actually, my boyfriend
在我走之前给我闹点事
just kinda sprung some news on me as I was leaving.
他想做什么 和朋友晚上出去玩
What's your guy want, a night out with the boys?
买新的卡车
New pickup truck?
其实他是想重新回到医学院
Actually, he's thinking about going back to medical school.
哇 你在和医生约会
Wow, you're dating a doctor.
下午茶来啦
New K-cups came in!
我要最好的法式香草
I need me my French vanilla supreme!
太棒了 拿一杯黑虎给我这个女人
Hells, yeah! And a black tiger for the con-woman!
我们要庆祝
We got to celebrate.
菲奥娜的未婚夫要成为医生了
Fiona's fiance is gonna be a doctor.
他不是我的未婚夫
He's not my fiance.
- 现在还不是 - 套牢他 姑娘
- Yet. - Put your hooks in him, girl.
医生都有钱得很
Doctors are rich.
太好啦 K杯[重用过滤器]到啦
All right, K-cups are in. Fantastic.
我们在庆祝菲奥娜未来的医生丈夫
We're celebrating Fiona's impending marriage to a doctor.
哦 哇 真的吗
Oh, wow. Really?
我 不 不一定
I-- no, not really.
你的K杯喜欢用哪种
Well, what flavor's your "K" cup poison?
- 我没用过 什么
- Never had one. - What?
来让我们带你参观公司的咖啡界
Well, let us usher you across the workplace coffee frontier.
她以后可不用这里了
She ain't gonna need a workplace much longer.
很快 她就会有仆人从银杯
Yeah, soon, she'll have her servants
里倒咖啡出来了
bringing her coffee out of a silver chalice.
好了 好了 别说啦
Okay, come on now, stop.
- 哦 - 不 我其实是说 继续吧
- Oh. - No, seriously, keep going.
早上好 曼迪
Morning, Mandy.
利普为什么这么在意那个贱人
Why does Lip give a fuck whether that bitch Karen
凯伦的死活
is alive or dead?
这是个迷
It's a mystery.
她又怎么了
What was all that about?
你 凯伦 莫测的男人心理
You, Karen, the unfathomable male soul.
你怎么没去学校
Why aren't you in school?
翘了
Skipping.
小黛比 我们家起码得有一个人不那么愤世嫉俗
Debs, we need at least one person in this family
我就指望你了
to not turn cynical, and my money's been on you.
我给希莉娅做了点汤
I made soup for Sheila.
很好 我会带去医院的
That's nice. I'm gonna drop by the hospital.
帮你送过去
I'll take it for you.
然后不劳而获地
And take the credit for doing something nice
得到赞扬
when you actually did nothing?
嘿 公平地说
Well, to be fair, at that point,
我得一路拿过去
I will have carried it all the way over there, so--
你觉得曼迪这样对你是理所当然
You're taking Mandy for granted.
为什么 她和你说什么了
Why? What'd she tell you?
她人好 为你付出了很多
She's kind, she's devoted,
你不能不在乎她的感受
she's not someone whose feelings you can ignore,
别当笨蛋了
so stop being a dope,
偶尔也替她想想吧
and put her feelings first every once in a while.
学校是个认识你的思维和
School is a time to experiment with your minds
生殖器的地方
and with your genitalia.
对我而言 人类的生殖器 是指引人类的
Now, the human genitalia, to me, is like a homing device--
指南针
God's compass. Huh?
我们每个人都有
And each of us has it,
它将我们引向命定的归宿
and it guides us to our destined homes.
如果我们强迫它指向一个它不想去的方向
Now, our devices don't work if we try to point 'em
它就会失灵
in a direction that they don't want to go in.
天哪 他得稍微收敛一点
He needs to tone it down, please.
就让人们自己做决定吧
But, you know, I laugh for a point,
听从他们
because let people chow down
自己的心
on the nether region of their choice--
男性 女性 动物
male, female, consenting animal.
停下
Stop-- uh...
梅森预科学院 谢谢你们
Mason Preparatory Academy, thank you so much...
- 谢谢 - 能倾听我们的故事
- Thank you. - ...for hearing our story.
谢谢 你们很棒
Thank you. You're terrific.
真的很棒
You guys are terrific.
- 抱歉 我 - 怎么回事
- I-- I'm sorry. It's-- I can't-- - What the hell was that?
是酒店的房间设施 我需要个迷你冰箱
It's the hotel. I need a mini-fridge.
至少给我个电炉
I need a hot plate at the very least.
- 我试着睡个午觉 - 打扰一下
- I tried to take a nap... - Excuse me?
- 但是我 - 打扰一下
- And I can't-- - Excuse me,
这是我听过的最真心的演讲
that was the most honest speech I've ever heard.
我刚刚给我爸发了短信 他同意我
I just texted my dad, and he told me
给你们捐款一千美元
I could donate $1,000 to the cause.
支票的收款人是
Um, who do I make the check out to?
"确信委员会"
"The Certitude Commission."
好的 好了
Okay. "Cert"-- okay.
停用镇静安眠剂和瘫痪药
Kill the phenobarbital and paralytics.
请问
Excuse me.
请问一下 嗨 抱歉 早上好
Excuse me, hi. I'm sorry. I know-- good morning.
我知道你很忙
I know you're really busy,
但是 你要"停用"什么
but what-- what are you "killing"?
她的脑部有涨水的现象
The swelling appears to have gone down in her brain,
所以我在停导致她昏迷的药物
so I'm killing the meds that induce the coma.
哦 是吗 请问
Oh, okay. Excuse me.
抱歉 那是什么意思
I'm sorry. What does that mean?
我要帮她停些药
I'm removing some of her meds.
- 是吗 抱歉 - 嘿
- Okay. N-- I'm sorry-- - Hey!
- 什么事 - 我是个好人
- Yes? - I'm a nice guy.
有耐心 一般情况下不喜欢使用暴力
Patient, not usually a violent dude,
但是你要是不用我们能懂得语言
but if you try to leave here one more time
解释清楚
without telling us what's going on
并试图离开的话
in words we can understand,
我会把你那小身躯举过头顶
I will your lift your tiny body over my head
从窗口扔下去
and throw you out the window.
她的脑部受到了重创
Your wife has sustained serious trauma to her brain.
所以你说你要撤掉
So you said that you're removing
那些让她昏迷的药
the meds that induce the coma.
她要醒了吗
Does that mean she's gonna wake up soon?
这是一种可能性
That is one possibility.
还有什么可能
What are the other possibilities?
她不会很快醒来
That she won't wake up soon,
或者永远醒不来
or that she won't wake up ever.
她要是醒过来 会好好的吗
But if she does wake up, will she be okay?
她醒过来之前我们也不知道
We won't know how much damage there is until she wakes.
我们能帮她清醒吗
Well, can we help her wake up?
她 她能听见我们的声音吗
Is she-- can she hear us in there?
没有人知道
Nobody knows,
我也不想被扔出窗外
and I don't want to get myself thrown out the window.
宝贝
Sweetie?
该醒醒了
Time to wake up.
培根 芹菜 西红柿夹在白面包里
Bacon, lettuce, and tomato on white,
就像你喜欢的那样
just like your other favorite meat.
没反应 我努力了很久耶
Really, nothing? I've been brewing that line for weeks.
我妈的生理期是明天
Mom's period day is tomorrow.
- 哦 - 你不知道吗
- Oh. - You didn't know that?
啊 拜托 V 我的脑容量就这么大
Ah, come on, V, I only got so much in the hard drive.
记住你妈的月经周期
Remembering your mom's menstrual cycle
可不是头号要紧的
is not a top priority.
要不我去超市买根验孕棒
Want me to go to Walgreen's, get a pee stick?
- 真的吗 - 难道我还能是开玩笑
- Honestly? - No, no, lie to me.
我听说那能加深夫妇感情
I hear it makes marriages thrive.
快吃
Eat.
我去买根验孕棒 然后打给你妈
I'll get a pee stick, we'll call your mom,
然后我们看着她用 会很好玩的
and we'll watch her take a piss. It'll be fun.
米奇居然要结婚了 你能相信吗
Mickey getting married, does that make sense to you?
为什么不
What sense needs to be made?
某人怀孕了 某人让她怀孕了
Someone's pregnant, someone got them pregnant,
这就是为什么会有婚姻在了
and that's... why marriage was invented.
他们约会很久了吗
They been going out long?
谁知道呢 他们搞的时候我又不在场
Who knows, I wasn't in on the courting, or the fucking.
他们在哪里见面呢
So where did they meet?
她在公园喷泉水疗馆工作
She works at Garden Springs Spa,
如果帮陌生人打飞机也算工作的话
if you call jerking off random dudes working.
她漂亮吗
She pretty?
用瞎眼的俄罗斯手妓标准来看
On the dead-eyed Russian hand-whore scale?
差不多七分吧
I'd say she'd rate about a seven.
- 你有低脂糖吗 - 没有
- You have sweet and low? - I do not.
没关系 我随身带着
It's okay. I always keep some in my wallet.
加进去就好
Just have to replace this one.
能受邀进入你情妇的门廊 我倍感荣幸
I feel so honored to be invited to your mistress' porch.
不请我进去坐坐吗
When will you invite me inside for scones?
不可能 听着
No time soon. Listen,
我在考虑去密歇根做个短期旅行
I'm thinking about taking a little vacation to Michigan.
不会又是要去偷车吧
I hope it's not to commandeer a shipment of cars.
我打算回去读医学院
I'm thinking of going back to medical school.
密歇根
In Michigan?
我没读完就走了 现在只剩下
I quit before I could finish, and I only have
几个学期就能拿到学位了
a couple of semesters left to get my degree,
- 所以 - 所以不是去度假
- so-- - So not a vacation?
不算是
Not exactly, no.
何必拐角抹弯 直说
So why the step-stutter? Why not tell me that
- 不就好了 - 是"拐弯抹角"
- from the beginning? - It's "stutter-step," okay?
我只是先试试水
I was testing the waters first.
对你我都有好处
It's good for me, and for you.
我会老老实实地 不惹麻烦
I'll be keeping out of trouble, keeping my nose clean.
在密歇根
In Michigan?
对
Yes.
我们可以去转转
I mean, we can go up there, drive around.
那里美食很多
I mean, great food. Excellent cheese. Truth.
先说服她搬家吧
Good luck convincing her to move.
- 菲奥娜 - 埃斯特法尼亚 混蛋
- Fiona? - Estefania, dammit!
你的妻子
your wife!
我的小宝贝
(Portuguese) Where is my little boy?
等下 要是我能说服 你去吧
Wait, is it-- but if I do, you're onboard?
你为什么认为我管事呢
Why is it you think I am in charge, huh?
- 管事 - 我不是管事的人
- Charge! - I'm not the one
谁才是呢 你是吗
who's in charge. Are you in charge?
你管事
You're in charge.
- 管事 - 我只会去我应该去的地方
- Charge. - I go where I'm supposed to go
做我应该做的事
and I do what I'm supposed to do, okay?
这样我才不会惹麻烦
If I do those things, I stay out of trouble.
建议你也这么做
I suggest you do the same.
- 鸡汤 - 哦
- Chicken soup. - Oh!
哦
Oh.
嘿 勤劳的小蜜蜂
Hey, busy beaver.
你知道什么叫"欲速则不达"吗
You know the phrase "speed kills"? It's true.
只是想把这些弄完
Just trying to get through this stack.
弄完这堆又会有一堆
Another stack just replaces this stack.
新的一堆在哪里呢
Where's the next stack?
学学慢的科学吧
Embrace the science of slow.
你在把K杯的活儿交给我之前
You shoulda thought about that before you made me
应该想到的
mainline K-cups.
我喝了一杯航空汽油 两罐黑虎
I've got a cup of jet fuel, two black tigers,
还有一颗奶油太妃糖
and a butter toffee in me.
我感觉精力充沛
I feel like I just did an eight ball.
你可不想干的太出色
You don't wanna raise the level of expectation
不然玛利亚病好回来可怎么办
for when Maria comes back from sick leave.
- 要慢 - 没错
- Science of slow. - Mm-hmm.
我去吃午饭 一起吗
I'm gonna grab some lunch. Wanna join?
- 我吃外带 - 来吧 我请你
- Brown-bagging it. - C'mon, my treat.
反正等你的医生老公赚钱了
You'll pay me back in spades
你也能请回我
when your doctor man starts his own practice.
- 来吧 来吧 - 好吧
- Come on, come on. - Okay.
嘿 这不是勃拉斯吗 [美国同性恋钢琴家]
Hey! If it isn't Liberace!
勃拉斯可是有钱人
Liberace was rich.
笑吧 尽情的嘲笑我吧 反正有人
Go ahead. Go ahead and mock, but I have found a constituency
能欣赏得了我的才华
willing to reward me for my talents.
盗窃和呕吐的才华
Larceny and vomiting?
雄辩 给我一瓶美格波本威士忌
Oratory. I'll have a Maker's Mark.
要那种 哦 别
Make it the good-- oh, come on.
你都欠了不少债了 弗兰克
You haven't paid your tab in months, Frank.
哦 不错嘛
Oh! Good for you!
那 给你留点零钱吧
Here, let me give you some change.
- 就五美元 - 我们不算利息
- 5 bucks? - You're lucky
算你走运了 弗兰克
we don't charge interest, Frank.
好久没见你这么干净过了 弗兰克
Haven't seen you this cleaned up in ages, Frank.
呃 二零零八年圣诞
Uh, Christmas, 2008.
你妈给我和你做了晚饭
Your mom made dinner for you and me,
然后就走了 我们还录了视频
then she went away, and you and I made the videotape.
你记得吗 视频还在吗
You remember that? You still have it?
那次真性感 我来了六七回
That was hot! I went six or seven rounds.
差不多是我最高记录了
That's close to my personal best.
弗兰克盖拉格
Frank Gallagher?
呃 不认识他
Uh, never heard of him.
请允许我自我介绍一下 我是阿利斯泰尔・赫德尔斯顿
Allow me to introduce myself. Alistair Huddleston.
我可以请你喝一杯吗
Can I buy you a drink?
两杯吧
Make it two.
敬男人
To men.
我为"重返乐园工程"工作
I work for "Return To Paradise Project."
我们是转型的政府部门
We're a transformational ministry
专攻性倾向转换疗法
specializing in conversion therapy.
我们让同性恋者重回健康的异性恋生活方式
We return homosexuals to healthy heterosexual lifestyles.
你为什么做这个
Why would you go do that?
我们相信同性恋是可以治愈的
We believe that homosexuality is curable.
虽然有些人乐在其中 但同性恋是一种毒瘾
Though some find pleasure in it, homosexuality is an addiction,
一种让家庭痛苦分离的毒瘾
an addiction that tears families apart.
我有个同性恋儿子 从来不用担心
I have a gay son. Never have to worry
他会搞大邻居烦人的荡妇的肚子
about him impregnating some skanky neighborhood slut
然后把她的小杂种带回家
and bringing home her unplanned-for half-breed.
我真希望当时就发现自己是同志
I wish I'd known I was gay back then.
我就可能在很多被同志一统江山的领域
I could've risen high in any one of the many fields
出人头地了 娱乐 政治
dominated by gays. Entertainment, politics,
广播
broadcasting.
网球
Tennis.
你现在为阿布汉姆 佩吉工作吗
You're working for Abraham Paige's agenda?
我是在扫除不平 在帮助被压迫的人
I'm cleaning up. Helping the oppressed.
他们是上了瘾 不是被压迫
They're addicted, not oppressed,
而且我们可以付你更多钱
and we can pay you more.
多多少
How much more?
固定薪水 住处 膳食
Stipend, room, board,
和可观的实现治疗的演讲费
and substantial speaking fees upon completion of therapy.
我拒绝治疗
I draw the line at therapy.
但弗兰克 没有治疗 就不能治愈
But Frank, see, without the therapy, there's no cure.
我们希望可以说治愈了你
I want to be able to say we cured you.
我现在是同志 我现在需要当同志
Gay is who I am now. Gay is who I shall be.
弗兰克 你曾经走过正确的道路
Frank, you once walked the true path
异性恋的道路
of heterosexual love.
如果我能让你回归正途
If I were to redirect you back onto that path,
你就会成为我们项目更有说服力的演讲者
you'll be a much more compelling speaker for our cause,
因为你就成了那个经历了炼狱之火后
because you'll have been singed by the fires of hell,
活着回来讲述的人了
but lived to tell.
我们的治疗有效
Our therapy works.
从厌恶疗法开始
It starts with aversion techniques,
控制你遏制进行同性性行为的苗头
conditioning you to avoid certain gay-sex triggers.
一旦你练习过这些治疗项目
Clinical fornication would start
我们就开始治疗性性行为了
once you've practiced some of those techniques.
抱歉 治疗性性行为
Sorry, clinical fornication?
我们会德拉克罗瓦酒店给你订房
We house you in the Delacroix Hotel,
然后送女人过去跟你滚床单
and deliver women to you to have sex with
直到你被治好
until you're cured.
抱 抱歉 打断一下 什么
I-I-I'm sorry, I interrupted you. What--?
我们觉得这样比鸡奸罪过轻点
We feel this is a lesser sin than sodomy.
我承认这不符合传统
I grant that this seems unconventional,
但为了阻止瘟疫蔓延就必须有新点子
but new ideas are necessary to counter unwavering plagues.
我们是在铺砌重归上帝的道路
We're paving a road back to God,
但魔鬼在路上竖起障碍
and the devil has erected obstacles
为了取得更好的效果 就需要打破常规
that call for rule-bending in service of a greater good.
给我点流动经费
Throw in some walking around money,
我可以试试
and I'll give it a shot.
要和米奇结婚的那个婊子
That whore that Mickey's marrying
是在春天花园水疗馆工作的真婊子
is an actual whore that works at Garden Springs Spa.
朋友和家人去打手枪打折吗
Friends and family discounts on handy-Js.
特里逼他搞她 好让他不要当同志
Terry made Mickey fuck her to fuck the gay out of him.
什么时候
When?
他抓到我们在一起之后
After he caught us together.
兄弟 我怎么不知道这事
Dude, how did I not know this shit?
我没告诉你
I didn't tell you.
有用吗
Well, did it work?
他假装过一两次
I mean, he might've faked it once or twice,
但是他想和我在一起
but he wants to be with me.
我知道他对我的感觉 是装不出来的
I know what he felt with me. You can't fake that.
但现在 这妞怀孕了
And now, this chick is pregnant.
伊恩 老弟 你应该放下了
Ian, my brother, you need to get out there
去找个新的来搞 好吗
and fuck someone new, okay?
找个二十来岁的
And someone in his early 20s,
不要像卡什或是奈德那样的老家伙
not some old dude like Kash or Ned.
操你妈
Fuck you.
好吧 真的 去同志酒吧
All right, seriously, go into a gay bar,
表明你的需要 然后满足需要
make your need known, and have at it.
曼迪因为你为了凯伦难过而难过
Mandy's upset you're upset about Karen.
天呐 曼迪跟多少人说了
Jesus. How many people is Mandy talking to?
她在乎你
She cares about you.
为什么 我不知道 你真是个白痴
Why... I don't know. You can be a real shithead.
为什么我们俩
How did we get this mixed up
都和米科维奇家的人纠缠不清呢
with two people from the Milkovich family?
- 家教不好 - 对
- Bad parenting. - Yeah.
两人份的牛排
Prime rib for two?
放那儿吧 对
Right there. Yeah. Oh.
这是你的
And here you go,
再一盘
and here you go.
盖拉格先生 请原谅我的唐突
Mr. Gallagher? Please excuse my informality,
但我看到你上了电视
but I saw you on TV, and just,
我代表整个同性恋团体
on behalf of the entire gay community,
感谢你勇于站在
I want to thank you for putting yourself
这政治问题的风口浪尖上
in the crosshairs of this political issue.
你的行为很勇敢也很鼓舞人心
I mean, it's courageous and inspiring.
您住在这时不管需要什么
Whatever you need while you are here...
- 呃 - 请尽管
- Uh... - ...please, just do not
- 提出来 - 番茄酱
- hesitate to ask. - Ketchup.
- 什么 - 番茄酱
- What? - Ketchup.
当然可以
Oh! Absolutely, yes.
我叫耶瑟斯
Um, my name is Jesus.
你需要我帮你定水疗服务吗 还是
Do you need me to sign you up for any spa treatments, or...
我明天很闲
Well, I'm wide-open tomorrow,
给我安排从早到晚的按摩
chockablock me some massages from sunup to sundown.
再来个面部美容
Throw in a facial.
好的 我会的
Okay-- will do.
番茄酱
Ketchup.
对
Oh, right!
我的牙齿可能
Is it possible that my teeth
自己长直吗
will spontaneously straighten out on their own?
吉米要回去读医学院了
Uh, Jimmy's going back to medical school.
我们可以请他帮忙
We can ask him to help.
我要酒
I need alcohol.
你妈还是没怀孕吗
Is your mom not pregnant again?
找不到她 去了她家 她工作的地方
Can't find her. Went to her house, her work.
她在躲我 肯定是坏消息
She's avoiding me. Must be bad news.
- 往好处想 - 之前两个月
- Think positive. - I've done that
一直往好处想的
for the past two months,
但她每次做尿检
and every time she pees on the stick,
都是坏消息 而且我一想到
it's bad news, and then I get depressed
我的老公搞了我的妈妈就很郁闷
thinking about my husband banging my mom,
因为我自私地希望宝宝有我们的基因
'cause we selfishly want to have a baby with some of our DNA--
而我妈可能再也怀不上了
and maybe my mom can't get pregnant anymore,
我们白白做了这么荒唐的事
and we've crossed this line for no reason,
而且我每次都会想起跟我老公滚床单的不是我
and every time I'm reminded it's not me banging my husband,
用验孕棒的不是我
and it's not me peeing on the stick,
生宝宝的也不是我
and it's not me that gets to have the baby!
V 如果不是为了你 你妈也不会这么做
V, your mom wouldn't be doing this if it wasn't for you.
阿凯会这么做也只是因为爱你
Kev's only doing this because he loves you.
如果不是你就不会有宝宝
There'd be no baby without you.
他们都那么爱你 一切都是为了你
They all love you so much. This is all about you.
所以你就喝喝酒 拿验孕棒
So you're gonna get some wine, get the stick,
带你妈去厕所 如果是坏消息
get your mom in the bathroom, and if you get bad news,
就醉一场
get drunk,
我们再去想接下来怎么办
and we'll figure out what comes next.
谁要沙士冰淇淋咖啡啊
Who needs root beer float coffee?
都要
All of us.
我爱你
I love you.
- 有消息了就打电话给我 - 谢谢
- Call me with the news. - Thank you.
黛比 卡尔 睡觉咯
Debs, Carl, bedtime!
看我的牙齿
See these?
你能给我买牙箍吗 就像给卡尔买的那个
Can you buy me braces like you paid for Carl's?
黛比 你的牙看起来还好啊
Aw, Debbie, they don't look so bad.
闭嘴
Shut up!
如果你的"还好"是一颗往这边
Yeah, if "not that bad" means one going this way
一颗往那边的话 那还好
and one going that way. Then yeah.
这样显得有个性
Well, they add character.
我长着红头发 满脸雀斑 和歪牙齿
I have red hair, freckles, and crooked teeth.
不需要再有个性了
Don't need any more character.
好吧 听着 我现在手头有点紧
Okay, listen, things are a little tight right now,
但是我会想办法 很快 我保证 好吗
but I'll make it happen, soon. I promise, okay?
所以
So...
医学院对吧
medical school, huh?
我 我是说 尝试了很多工作
I... I mean, I put in a ton of work,
然后觉得我可能应该回去
and I just got thinking that maybe I should go back
完成没做完的 我
and finish what I started. I--
- 我觉得很好 - 真的吗
- I think it's great. - Really?
嗯
Yeah.
你很聪明 你关心他人
You're smart, you care about people,
你是个好人
you're a good person.
给卡尔买牙箍 给黛比买牙箍
Getting Carl braces, Debbie braces,
照顾利亚姆
taking care of Liam.
看看你有多关心我们
Look how much you cared for all of us,
又没有什么回报
without getting much in return.
嘿 我收到了很多回报
Hey, I get plenty in return.
我会一直支持你
I'm behind you all the way. Mwa!
真的吗
Really?
因为我很需要
'Cause I'm gonna need it.
很多的工作 很多时间
Plenty of work. Plenty of hours.
你会去哪所学校
So where would you go?
芝加哥大学 西北大学
University of Chicago? Northwestern?
西北大学估计不错
Northwestern could work.
对 就登记入学 但是
Yeah, just gotta check into it, but...
有很多选择
plenty of options.
"吉米医生"
"Dr. Jimmy."
听起来很高端啊
That'd be something, huh?
医生
Doctor!
嘿
Hey.
- 你的房间怎么样 弗兰克 - 设备要修了
- How's your room, Frank? - Amenities need to be amended.
这些迷你瓶太小了
These mini-bottles are a little too mini.
我要换点大瓶子的
I need to get some of the big boys up here.
我会的
Will do.
我带了些录影 开始转换治疗前
I brought you some media that needs to be viewed
你要先看看
before we can begin the conversion process.
没问题 我就从这张片看起
Okey-dokey. I'll get started on this one pronto.
你结过婚吗
You have been married before?
没离过呢 但她从来没真的让我开心
Still am, but she never really floated my boat.
我尽了丈夫的责任让她幸福
I did my husbandly duty to keep her happy,
但从来没有快乐
but it was always without pleasure
或乐趣
or joy.
- 有孩子吗 - 有几个
- Kids? - A few.
也就是说你已经
So you have committed the loving act
跟异性做过爱了
of heterosexual copulation?
坦白说 那也是因为醉酒的缘故
It was always under the influence, frankly.
小弟弟总要做点事的
Had to get the plumbing to work.
不 我们认为你只是脱轨了
No, we think you just got sidetracked.
根据你之前与女性交往的经历
With your history of female contact,
我们可以立即着手治疗你的淫乱病症
we can begin the clinical fornication stage immediately.
我很怀疑它的有效性 不过如果你认为它可能有用的话
I doubt it'll work, but I'll give it my best efforts
我会尽力配合
if you think it might help.
员工们 你们好啊
Hello, cuppers!
我的高曾祖父
My great-great-grandfather
曾经在内战中打过仗
fought in the war between the states.
他从那次战争中回来的时候心中有了一个目标
He came back from that war with one goal in mind.
那就是发明一种一次性的杯子 这样就不用
To invent a disposable cup so he wouldn't have to wash...
洗"这该死的杯子了"
"The same stupid cup every doggone time!"
好消息 我们已经获得批准
Good news! We have received approval...
嘿 菲奥娜 你玩垒球的吗
Hey, Fiona, you play softball?
- 呃 不玩 - 从来不玩吗
- Uh, no. - Never?
- 嘘 马特叔叔正在讲话 - 嗯
- Shh! Uncle Matt's talking. - Mm.
干得好维尼 皮塔罗
Nice job, Vinny Pitaro!
- 维尼 维尼 - 嘿, 维尼
- Vinny! Vinny! - Hey, Vinny!
他在那
There he is!
我们有个名为"纸杯人"的球队
So we have a team called "The Cuppers,"
今晚的比赛我希望你能去给我当拉拉队
and I need you on the squad for tonight's game.
说实话 我很菜的
Really, I'm-I'm-I'm terrible.
噢 " 自从我上一次穿上防滑鞋以来
Oh, " it was back before the millennium
已经有好几百年了 "
when I last donned me cleats. "
- 这是什么调调 - 呃 我想可能是坏坏的英国腔吧
- What accent is that? - Uh, bad British I think.
- 嗯哼 - 是的
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
在许多卡车的后挡板上
...thousands of cups
都有杯子
at many a tailgate!
去拿吧 伙计们
Go get 'em, cuppers!
去吧 这个联盟有男也有女的
So come on, the league's coed,
你知道的 我们需要多一点女士 不然可要输的
so, you know, we need more ladies or we gotta forfeit.
好吧 我懂了 我懂了 你是医生的妻子
All right, I get it. I get it. You're a doctor's wife.
你知道 你得保持形象
You know, you gotta keep up appearances.
不能跟同事一起玩乐
Can't have fun with your co-workers
也不能有自己的生活 我完全懂的
or a life for yourself. Totally understand.
好 好吧 短信告诉我地点
O-o-okay, fine.Text me where the field is,
如果我想活动下筋骨的话
and if I feel like blowing out a knee...
我会去的
I'll be there.
很好 可别错过了哦
All right! Hey, you're not gonna want to miss it, either.
比赛结束后我们再来点大麻吧
We pop a pony keg of bud after.
- 只是说说而已 - 说说而已哦
- Just sayin'. - Just sayin'.
请问 你知道我能在哪儿
Excuse me, do you know where I might
找到弗兰克盖拉格吗
be able to find Frank Gallagher?
很有可能在最近的监狱或者贫民窟吧
Best bet, nearest jail or gutter.
麻烦你告诉他阿布汉姆在找他
Would you tell him that Abraham is looking for him,
并且让他通过这个电话号码找我好吗
and that he can reach me at that number?
额 如果有小费的话我会记得更牢哦
Uh, I remember best when I'm tipped to do so.
阿布汉姆先生 我会确保他收到你的消息的
Mr. Abraham, I will see to it that he gets your message.
多谢
Thank you.
- 弗兰克 这是斯科特- 嗨 弗兰克
- Frank, this is Scotty. - Hi, Frank.
能给我们两分钟时间吗 我
Could you excuse us just one second? I--
我是不会停止操男人
I am not gonna stop fucking men
而转而去操长得像男人的女人的
to start fucking women who look like men.
这是个部门而不是妓院
This is a ministry, not a brothel.
那些有所准备的志愿者
The volunteers who are ready
都已经相互组好队了
are teamed with others who are ready.
谢谢你能在此跟我合作
Thanks for being here and doing this with me.
斯科特和我们一起已经六个月了
Scotty's been with us for six months of hard,
这期间她一直很认真很努力地
devoted work
想要克服她的女同性恋倾向
trying to overcome her lesbian tendencies.
你们俩要互相帮助
You're going to help each other.
这段路很长 但是我想听从上帝的旨意
It's been a long road, but I want to be right with God.
弗兰克也一样 难道不是吗 弗兰克
As does Frank. Don't you, Frank?
信仰上帝总是好的
It's always good to have God in your corner.
这个舞台的目的就是刺激彼此
The goal of this stage is to stimulate one another,
看看刺激是否能让你们性交并达到性高潮
and see if stimulation can lead to copulation and orgasm.
好吧 呃 你们已经迫不及待了
Okay, uh, you're anxious to go.
趁你们还没脱光我得走了
I'm gonna slip out before you slip off anything else.
真要这么做吗
Is this really happening?
这是上帝的旨意 上次他
God willing. The last time Alistair
带一个男人来见我时 我脱了衣服后
brought a man in to see me, he left in tears
他哭着离开了 上次我还刮毛了
after I got undressed. Last time I shave everything.
斯科特已经采取了避孕措施
Scotty has been taking birth control,
但是为了防止性病
but as an extra precaution against STDs,
还请戴上保险套吧
please use the condoms
我给你们买好放在浴室里了
I provided for you in the bathroom.
像亚当和夏娃一样 第一次在伊甸园里
Be like Adam and Eve, discovering one another
探索彼此吧
for the first time in the Garden of Eden
赤裸着探索彼此 给彼此带来
naked, discovering each other, bringing to each other
上帝给你们准备的快乐吧
the pleasure that God intended for them.
不用觉得丢脸也不用觉得自责 其他一切
No shame, no guilt, no knowledge of things
分散你们对做爱的注意力的东西都不用管
that distract us from God's love.
# 起来吧 起来吧 #
Get up, get up
# 醒来吧 醒来吧 #
Wake up, wake up, wake up
# 噢 宝贝 今晚我们开始吧 #
Oh, baby, now, let's get down tonight
唔 我得承认你的乳房长得很漂亮
Well, I must say, you have amazing cans.
- 以前肖恩娜也这么说过 - 肖恩娜是谁
- Shawna used to say that. - Who's Shawna?
一个我尽力想忘记的人
Someone I'm trying to forget.
你能帮助我忘记她吗
Will you please help me... forget her?
# 宝贝 #
And baby
# 我把持不住了 #
I can't hold it much longer
唔 往下面摸
Well, hello down there.
噢 上帝也想让我们这么做
Oh, God wants this for us.
你知道吗 也许 也许他是对的
You know what? Maybe-- maybe he's right.
如果你注定是个女同性恋
If you were supposed to be a lesbian
我注定是个男同性恋的话
and I was supposed to be gay,
他一定是软的
he'd be limp,
但是你看 我的小弟弟硬起来了
and look, my loaf of bread riseth.
你以前曾经摸过男人的小弟弟吗
You ever felt one of those before?
从没摸过这么老的
Never one this old.
谢谢
Thanks.
它就像一颗山胡桃树 一年年地长大
It's like a hickory tree. Gets stronger every year.
你还好吗
You okay?
- 是的 - 你今天没去学校
- Yeah. - You weren't at school today.
噢 没去 没赶上
Oh, no, I didn't make it.
凯伦还好吗
Karen?
她情况特别糟糕
She's in pretty bad shape.
今晚晚些时候你会过去吗
You going over there later tonight?
我不知道
I don't know.
我真的不确定
I'm not really sure.
待会你想让我过去吗
Do you want me to come over later?
我昨晚很想你
I missed you last night.
好的
Sure.
是的 请务必来
Yes, please.
好的 回头见
Okay, I'll see you later.
好的
Okay.
你在上面感觉怎样
How's it going up there?
- 挺好的 - 因为 你也知道
- Fine. - Cause, you know,
我一直看不到你的脸
I haven't seen your face for awhile,
而且你也说得不多
and you're not saying much.
- 真的挺好的 - 嗯 唔
- It's fine. - Okay, well,
我有个约定要遵守
I got an appointment that I've got to make,
我们怎样才能让你达到高潮呢
so what can we do to get you where you need to be?
正在尝试中
Trying.
我能做点什么来加快你达到高潮的进程呢
Is there anything I could do to hurry it up?
我也不知道
Not sure.
你把我想象成安吉丽娜・朱莉看看
What if you were to imagine that I'm Angelina Jolie?
# 别让我一个人 #
Don't leave me hanging
因为你也知道 有这么些人需要
Cause you know, I got these people that need--
别说话 安吉
Shut up please, Angie!
# 我只是想要一个能说说话的人 #
I just want someone that I can talk to
# 我想要的就是你的本来面目#
I want you just the way you are
# 我要知道你将会永远不变 #
I need to know that you will always be
她讨厌这首歌
She hates that song.
我很抱歉 真的
I'm sorry. I'm really--
听着 我知道你们一整天都待在这里
look, I know you're here all day,
你们也只是想要唤醒她
and you're just trying to wake her up.
你知道的 我只是想 如果你们想要唤醒她
I just think, you know, if you want to wake her up
你们应该要做她喜欢的事 而不是她不喜欢的
you should do shit she likes, not shit she hates.
她讨厌那首歌
She hates that.
你觉得她会喜欢什么
What do you think she would like?
我也不知道 呃 可能是别的什么东西吧
I don't know, uh, something else.
我去买咖啡
I'm gonna go get some coffee.
不 乔迪 听着 我并不是故意
No, Jody, look, I didn't mean to--
不 兄弟 你 你说得对
No, man, you're-- you're right.
你一直是她很好的朋友
You've been a good friend to her.
情况有没有好点
Any progress at all?
唔 有时候她的脚尖会动一下
Well, she flicks her toes sometimes,
但是医生说这可能只是生理反射作用
but the doctor thinks it could just be reflexes.
嗯
Right.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
别说抱歉 我总是想
Don't be sorry. I've often thought
乔迪的演奏曲目可能会有些帮助
Jody's musical repertoire could use some updating.
不 呃 我真的很抱歉 我
No, uh, I'm sorry, I--
我对凯伦不够好
I wasn't very nice to Karen...
我最后一次见到她的时候
the last time I saw her.
事实上 我 呃 我几乎是要跟她分手了
Actually, I, uh... I kind of ended it,
而且我并没有处理好
and I didn't do it very well,
我不希望那就成为她最后从我这里听到的话
and I don't want that to be the last she heard from me.
不会的
It won't be.
我们都很乐观 会有好转的
We're thinking positive. Makes a difference.
她会醒过来的
She's gonna wake up,
你并没有惹她难过 利普
and you didn't make her sad, Lip.
当她收到你的短信的时候 她特别开心
She was so happy when she got that text from you.
她知道你是想发短信来跟她和解
She knew you were texting to make up.
你应该看看她有多高兴的
You should've seen her light up.
- 短信 - 就在那个她去见你
- Text? - The night of the accident,
却出了车祸的晚上
when she came to meet you.
我真的感觉到她特别激动
I honestly think that she was so excited,
她只是忘了往两边看看
she just forgot to look both ways.
凯伦的手机在这里吗
Do you have Karen's phone here?
应该是跟她其他东西放在一起了
it could be with her things.
我想 呃
I think, um...
# 当你清早醒来 #
When you wake up in the morning
够了 小妞们 走开
That's enough, girls! Walk away.
雷尼 走开
Renee, walk away.
我一直在到处找你
I've been looking all over for you!
我手机没电了 你又没给我个充电器
My cell phone died. You didn't leave me a charger.
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
我人脉广 弗兰克
I know people, Frank.
我放话出来了 他们打电话找的
I put the word out, they call.
我给你找了个好点的旅馆
I got you a better hotel.
是给大使住的套房 在北州街街上
This is for the Embassy Suites, North State Street.
快点喝完好出发 穿好衣服
Finish your drink, head over, get dressed.
衣柜里有干净的保罗衫和卡其制服
There's clean polos and khakis in the closet.
给你在奥斯卡・王尔德书店找了份临时工 今晚开始工作
Your next gig is at the Oscar Wilde Bookstore, tonight.
- 好吧 - 表现利落点
- Okay. - Look sharp.
嘿 我一直在找你呢
Hey! I've been trying to find you.
我一直在避免被你找到呢
I've been avoiding you finding me.
- 妈咪 - 我感觉觉不舒服呢
- Mama. - I'm not feeling well,
每当我感觉不舒服的时候总有坏消息出现
and when I don't feel well, it's usually bad news.
别这样 也可能是好消息啊
No, it could be good news.
上两次你感觉挺好的
The last two times,you felt fine
但却是坏消息 所以这次也许是好消息
and it was bad news, so maybe this time it's good news.
不 不可能
No, I don't think so.
妈妈 我十分感谢你之前和现在
Mama, I really appreciate all you've done
为我所做的一切
and continue to do for me.
把验孕棒给我
Gimme the stick.
- 这次我能跟你一起去吗 - 不行
- Can I go with you this time? - No!
卫生间是有门的
Bathrooms have doors for a reason.
我在里面嘘嘘 你在外面等着
I'll do the whizzing, you do the waiting.
不要抱太大希望
Keep your hopes in check.
好啦 大家都把外套穿上
All right,everyone grab your jackets,
也许会冷 而且我也不想等你们
it might be cold, and I don't want to wait for you.
- 走开 - 嗨
- Get off! - Hey!
嗨 饿了吗
Hey! Hungry?
意大利面和面包 我做的给你留了一些
Spaghetti and bread. I made them leave you some.
谢谢 工作怎么样
Thanks. How was work?
很好啊 很不错
It was good.It was great, actually.
今晚我被邀请去打垒球了
I got invited to play softball tonight.
你连手套都没有
You even own a glove?
是芝加哥式的垒球 根本就不需要手套
It's Chicago-style softball. You don't need a glove.
- 看看你 正在融入他们啊 - 嗯
- Look at you, trying to fit in. - Hmm.
我希望他们能留住我一会儿
I'm hoping they keep me around for a while.
一起来吧 应该挺好玩的 结束之后我们可以去喝点东西
Come with. It should be fun. We can grab a drink after.
- 你可以见见大家 - 不错
- You can meet everyone. - Cool.
我也许会去密歇根呆几天
Hey, I may have to spend some more time in Michigan.
- 什么 - 医学院
- What? - Med school.
行政部叫我去的 他们说
Admissions Department called and said
我必须结课了 否则我将被扣掉很多学分
that I have to finish up there or I lose a bunch of credits.
我可以申请本地的学校 但如果这样的话
I can apply for schools here, but I'd basically
我就必须从头来过 以前做的都白费了
have to start over, and lose all the work I've already done.
只要一年就好了
It's only for a year.
我知道这有点美中不足
I know it's a bit of a fly in the ointment,
但他们能让我重新入学已经很好了
but they're being really cool, letting me re-enroll.
- 没有别的选择了吗 - 不见得有
- There's no other option? - Not really.
不见得有还是没有
What--not really, or no?
没有
No.
哇 这真是... 哇
Wow, that's... wow.
- 你可以跟我一起去 - 去密歇根
- You can come with me. - To Michigan?
也不是很远啊
It's not that far.
孩子呢
W-- the kids?
一起来啊 如果你想的话
Yeah, sure, if you want.
- 我想的话 - 一起来 当然 他们也一起来
- If I want? - Yes, yes, of course, them too.
听着 有很多事情需要处理
Look, there's details to sort through,
但都是可以解决的啊 全部都可以解决
but they're all doable details,totally doable details.
啊哈 啊
Uh-huh. Uh...
我得去为打垒球做准备了
I have to get ready for softball.
大家注意了 凯文要做爸爸了
Attention, people! Kevin is gonna be a daddy!
天啊
Holy shit!
万岁
Hooray!
真的吗 真的吗
Really? Really?
大家来看验孕结果
Look at the stick, people!
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
快看这根棒子 快看这根棒子
Look at this stick! Look at this stick!
注意了 今天晚上
Be aware, for the rest of the night,
我要用这根验孕棒调鸡尾酒了
I am stirring cocktails with this stick!
弗兰克 你到底在哪
Frank, where the hell are you?
快回电话
Call me.
嗨 真不敢相信你这么快
Hey. I can't believe you texted me
就给我发信息了
for a second go around.
也许我回来是错误的
Maybe I made a mistake coming back.
- 不 不 不 别这样 - 嗯
- No, no, no, no. Come on.- Mmm.
我们都是被异性恋的魔力吸引住的
We are heteros trapped in the demonic obsession
同性恋
of same-sex sin.
我们必须要远离那些同性恋
We must rid ourselves of the gay.
我们只需要继续练习
We just have to keep practicing.
# 你如何崛起 然后又坠落 #
It's how you get up, then you fall
加油 麦克 加油 来个全垒打
Let's go, Mike! Come on, bring us home!
菲奥娜很喜欢垒球啊
Fiona's so into softball, huh?
我们需要更多这样的人 科尼
We need more of that around here, Connie.
- 麦克 了结他 - 加油 麦克
- Mike, end this thing! - Yeah, Mike!
接下来的回合我们啤酒不够了
We don't have enough beer for extra innings.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God!
放我下来 放我下来
Put me down! Put me down!
啤酒 我们去喝点啤酒
Beer! Let's get some beer!
我们要做最坏的打算了吗
Should we be planning for the worst?
她经历过巨大的创伤
She's been through a tremendous trauma,
但奇迹确实发生了
but I've seen miracles. They do happen.
继续和她说话
Just keep engaging with her,
做些她喜欢的事情也许会唤醒她
doing things she likes that might trigger her unconscious.
让她知道你们在这里陪着她
Let her know you're here.
希莉娅...
Sheila...
今晚你得回家睡会
you should go home tonight, get some sleep.
希莉娅
Sheila,
我觉得我们现在得轮流值班
I think we need to start taking turns
闭上眼睛躺在床上好好睡会儿
getting some shut-eye in a real bed.
- 我觉得 - 请别说
- I think-- - Please don't say that.
- 请别 - 我不会说
- Please. - I'm not saying
- 她不会醒过来的 - 乔迪
- she's not gonna wake up.. - Jody
我只是想说这是一场持久战 而不是短跑冲刺
I'm just saying it's a marathon, not a sprint.
我们也要好好照顾自己 为了凯伦
We gotta start taking care of ourselves, for Karen.
你真是个王子 乔迪
You're a prince, Jody.
别说这个
Stop.
你真是个王子
You're like a prince.
我觉得你是她的王子
And I-- I think that you're her prince.
当她还是个小女孩的时候
When-- when she was a little girl,
我会给她读旧童话书里的故事
I would read to her from this old, old book of fairy tales.
那种黑暗又老旧 扭曲而又恐怖的故事
They're dark, the old ones. They're twisted and scary,
她会握住我的手 紧紧地抓住
and she would hold my hand and squeeze it really tight
当女巫和毒苹果
when the witches and the poisoned apples--
真爱之吻这些桥段出来的时候
and wait for the kiss of true love, and when it came,
她就会笑着说 "妈妈 再读一次"
she would smile and say "mama, read it again."
她长大了 我带走了她的王子
She grew up,and I took her prince.
你是她的
You're hers.
好了 兄弟们 真是场精彩的比赛 谢谢你们把我算上
All right, cuppers, good game,guys. Thanks for having me.
什么 不 你已经喝了
What? No, you-- what? You've had, like,
- 一半的啤酒了 - 干了剩下的
- a half of a beer. - Pound the rest of it, girl!
事实上 应该是"半干"
Actually, that would be "half pounding" it.
是的 是的 是的 别忘了马特叔叔的准则
Yeah, yeah, yeah, hey, Uncle Matt's rules.
所有球员在球赛胜利的第二天
All cuppers get to come in two hours late
可以迟到半小时
the day after a softball victory.
马特叔叔鼓励酗酒哦
Uncle Matt encourages drunkenness.
- 别这样 - 是的 跟我们一起喝吧
- Stop it. - Yeah, please, drink with us.
我跟我哥哥说好了只待一小会
I told my brother I'd only stay for a second.
那些小屁孩得在午夜前上床睡觉
Those little ones gotta be in bed before midnight.
你有几个小孩
How many of those kids are yours?
我一个都还没生但我负责照顾所有的
I birthed none yet I'm responsible for all.
等你嫁给了那个医生
Wait until you marry the doctor,
你就会有你自己的爱尔兰宝宝了
you'll have your own Irish brood.
啊 加油 兄弟们
Uh, go cuppers!
加油 兄弟们
Go cuppers!
干了它
Finish that.
- 噢 谢谢 再见 - 好吧
- Oh, thank you. Bye! - All right.
那一定就是那位医生了
That must be the doctor.
我有那么聒噪吗
Did I do that out loud?
- 有 - 好吧 兄弟们
- Yup. - All right, guys,
算了 算了 快别盯着看了
come on, come on, stop staring.
- 为什么 -业余者们
- Why? - Amateurs.
我们有盯着看吗
Were we staring?
比赛怎么样
How was the game?
三振 我得分了
Walk-off win. I scored.
你早就知道了 是吧
You knew, didn't you?
- 知道什么 - 密歇根
- Knew what? - Michigan.
你早就知道你会搬回去从头开始
You knew you were gonna have to move back from the beginning.
什么 没有
What? No.
请别撒谎
Please don't be the guy who lies!
Please, don't be that guy.
是的 可能 不确定 但是的
Yes... probably. N-not for sure, but yes.
- 我累了 兄弟 - 菲奥娜
- I'm tired, dude. - Fiona.
- 菲奥娜 - 干嘛
- Fiona! - What?
我需要一个转机
I need a change.
从我这里吗
From me?
我不是这个意思
You know that's not what I meant.
很显然 当你决定你要告诉我
Clearly, I only know what you want to tell me
我才知道你想说什么
when you decide you want to tell it to me.
我爱你
I love you.
很好
Great.
黛比需要矫正器
Debbie needs braces.
我煮浓咖啡 你在卖杯子
I'm making espressos, you're selling cups.
只是一年而已
It's a year.
别说了好吗 好像这一年什么也不是
Stop saying it like a year is nothing,
好像这一年什么都不会发生
like nothing can happen in a year,
好像我们离开彼此一年一点关系也没有
like being away from each other for a year wouldn't matter!
别人也这样啊
Other people do it.
我累了
I'm tired.
明早我得早起
I gotta get up early in the morning.
卖杯子
Selling cups.
菲奥娜
Fiona?
我会做一个好医生的
I'm gonna be a great doctor.
我不要跟你吵
I'm not arguing that.
你醒着吗
Are you awake?
噢 给我 蕾哈娜 是的 哦
Oh, give it to me, Rihanna! Yeah! Oh, yeah!
开门
Open the door.
快点 就要到了 哦 快到了
Go! Almost there. Oh, almost there!
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
我 我可以解释的
I-I can explain.
同性恋恢复治疗吗
Reparative therapy?
天啊 把她给我弄出去
Jesus, get her out of here.
但我可以扳直他的
But I can fix him.
- 我会更努力 - 滚
- I can try harder. - Get--!
- 我可以的 - 天啊 丢她出去
- I can do it! - Jesus, get her out!
你被阿利斯泰尔・赫德尔斯顿 的
You let yourself be brainwashed by Alistair Huddleston
"重返乐园项目"洗脑了吗
and his "Return To Paradise Project" lunatics?
我以为她是男的
I thought she was a he.
她可是穿着彭德尔顿格子还有军靴
She was wearing Pendleton plaid and combat boots.
伐木巨人的蓝公牛也会被愚弄的
Paul Bunyan's blue ox would have been fooled.
她只差一把斧子了 [指鸡鸡]
All she needed was an axe.
耶瑟斯 锁门
Jesus, lock the door.
我是同性恋
I'm gay!
耶瑟斯 等一下 我是同性恋
Hey, Jesus, wait. I'm gay.
我百分之百是同性恋
I'm completely 100% gay.
好吧
Good.
现在你要证明一下
Now you're gonna prove it.
上
Boys.
我喜欢看
I like to watch.
哦 男的
Oh, boy.
我是说 噢 男的
I mean, oh, boy!
所以你说你"下去"
So when you say you "went down--"?
我下去了直捣中心
I went down and I went to town.
我舔着她就好像在品尝珍馐美味
I chowed down on her like I was drinking from a cup of ambrosia,
然后她来了 她来了
and she came! She came to.
你要明白我说的话
You gotta get the word out.
我发现了治愈昏迷的方法
I found the cure to comas!